New year. Old friends.
Happy New Year, Charlie Brown is a family, animation,
comedy film directed by Sam Jaimes.
It's the night of Peppermint Patty’s New Year’s Eve bash, but Charlie
Brown has to write a book report about War and Peace.
Hoping to join the fun for a special dance with the Little
Red-Haired Girl, he tries desperately to finish in time.
Charlie Brown (voice), played by Chad Allen.
Peppermint Patty (voice), played by Kristie Baker.
Linus van Pelt (voice), played by Jeremy Miller.
Lucy van Pelt (voice), played by Melissa Guzzi.
Schroeder (voice), played by Aron Mandelbaum.
Marcie (voice), played by Jason Mendelson.
Happy New Year, Charlie Brown!
is the 30th prime-time animated television special based
upon the comic strip Peanuts, by Charles M.
It aired on the CBS network on January 1, 1986, at 8:30 p.m.
The special focuses on Charlie Brown's difficulty
finishing a book report over the holidays.
The special is dedicated to longtime Peanuts animator Bernard
Gruver, following his death on June 14, 1985.
Another New Year's special, Snoopy Presents: For Auld Lang Syne,
was released on Apple TV+ on December 10, 2021.
The tone is lighthearted.